

BHARAT NAGDEV

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

I'm a Frontend developer with over four years of experience working in the tech industry, providing valuable expertise to different products and services and working with a team of experienced professionals. I aim to learn frontend technologies and grow my career in it.

9173217799

B/101, The Sun Residency-1, old Sindhunagar, Bhavnagar

n.bharat.gh@gmail.com bharatnagdev.github.io

in LinkedIn: @bharat-nagdev-

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

I've worked with various types of projects and have worked on programming languages and coding frameworks such as Angular & ionic. I have also tried on IOT projects development.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

GLS UNIVERSITY

MASTER OF COMPUTER APPLICATION, JUNE 2016 - MAY 2018

- Graduated with first class distinction
- Graduate in JavaScript and mobile application development
- Awarded with most supportive student of the batch

SSCCS GURUKUL, BHAVNAGAR

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION, JUNE 2013 - MAY 2016

- Graduated With first class
- Participated in national level soft skills development
- participated in annual state level IT event and secured first rank for game developed (Flash'14-15)
- Achieved 2nd rank in quiz competition (Flash'14-15)

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

ASCENT INFO SOLUTION | OCT 2022 - PRESENT

• Started working with React JS & React native and developing an Event management system.

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

BIZTECHCS | JUNE 2020 - OCT 2022

- Worked as key resource for an industry based software service including client communication
- Managed team of 3 developers
- Additionally, organising cultural events as member of culture group of organisation

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

BIZTECHCS | JUNE 2018 - MAY 2020

- Developed and designed asset management products
- Worked as key resource in medical Industry based software service
- Additionally, organising cultural events as member of culture group of organisation













